{"data":[{"question":"While Diana watched her favorite television program, there was a power cut.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While","b":"watched","c":"favorite","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Watched-> was watching","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I will tell you my news when I will see you tomorrow.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will tell","b":"my","c":"when","d":"will see","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Will see-> see","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"There are such many places of interest in London that Jane can't decide where to go first.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"such","b":"interest","c":"can't","d":"where","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Such-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Our new teacher gave an interesting lecture at Spain history.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Our","b":"gave","c":"interesting","d":"at","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- At-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"You can't withdraw any money unless you don't show us your identity card.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can't withdraw","b":"any","c":"don't show","d":"identity","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Don't show-> show","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"She has so many money that she can buy whatever she wants to.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"so many","c":"can buy","d":"whatever","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- So many-> so much","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"It is such a boring book that nobody like it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"such","c":"boring","d":"like","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Like-> likes","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The scientist wanted to know who has been trying to stop the experiment.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The scientist","b":"who","c":"has been trying","d":"to stop","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Has been trying-> had been trying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"He wanted to know if had I seen Mary the day before.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wanted","b":"if","c":"had","d":"the day before","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Had I seen-> I had seen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"She decided to go to bed because the television program was bored.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to go","b":"because","c":"television","d":"bored","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Bored-> boring","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}